[
    {
        "question": "How many sisters does Joey have?",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many claps are there in the theme tune?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many long stemmed roses did Ross send to Emily?",
        "answer": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the comic Phoebe stole from Ross when she mugged him as a teenager?",
        "answer": "Science Boy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's Joey's fake name?",
        "answer": "Ken Adams"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Rachel's boss who Chandler dates?",
        "answer": "Joanna"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did Carol meet Susan?",
        "answer": "Gym"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Phoebe initially change her name to after marrying Mike?",
        "answer": "Princess Consuela Bananahammock"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chandler and Ross were once thrown out of a concert by which band?",
        "answer": "Wham!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Mike's profession before turning professional pianist?",
        "answer": "Lawyer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Chandler's roomate Eddie's fish?",
        "answer": "Buddy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Ross and Chandler's band?",
        "answer": "Way No Way"
    },
    {
        "question": "What product is advertised on the back of the Playboy in which Ross' joke is printed?",
        "answer": "Grand Marnier"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Joey's PIN number?",
        "answer": "5639"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times did Monica's date see Star Wars?",
        "answer": "317"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which part of her body has Rachel has plastic surgery on?",
        "answer": "Nose"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state do Ross and Emily end up in after their first date?",
        "answer": "Vermont"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Treeger, the super, think that Joey's nickname is?",
        "answer": "Chick"
    },
    {
        "question": "What nationality is Joey 1/16th?",
        "answer": "Portuguese"
    },
    {
        "question": "What advertising slogan did Ross claim to have invented?",
        "answer": "Got Milk?"
    }
]
